{
    "id": "921e3f9d811846ec902d15b31bee03e5",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My windows look ……………… the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "upon",
                "out on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbd96ad3ec95456aa998e04aa30031ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have prepared a rough ………………. of the report.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "draft",
                "drought",
                "draught"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d46298e6e3ec4a12b93b9c99314e1840"
        },
        {
            "question": "The reward was not commensurate ………………. the work done by us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3df8ea44245046ac9030912f0fa81b7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care ………………… the expense I want the party to be a real success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb17ad47434a4a4eb7901ed1775bbd7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Vinay does not play cricket, and …………….. does Yeshwant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "so",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d9f113577ff4aba92353420be63e12d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "so",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d9627df361a405ea1cb9310af287e11"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither did she come ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she didn't write",
                "nor she wrote",
                "nor did she write"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ce276f116c74ac1b98ad9f7de2aa71c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking is injurious to health, …………………. you smell bad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well as it makes",
                "it makes",
                "as well as making"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "33e64a6099714c12af2a893c1ae0185f"
        },
        {
            "question": "On the stand there were newspapers and magazines of ……………….. kind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "any",
                "whole"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9642c056beb447ca296771f759f7b1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If the teacher was to walk in now, we ……………… in real trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd614769c26d427c9a0366417575bf9e"
        }
    ]
}